Hi!
I'm here showing you how to wash your jeans.
Right now I'll tell you how to load the washing machine.
You want to go ahead and add your detergent to the washing machine first.
You always want to put your detergent in first, then go ahead, and put your jeans in.
Be careful not to stuff them into the washing machine.
You need a little bit of space between things in order for the stuff to get through, the water and the soap to really get in there and wash it.
It's never a good idea to stuff your clothes in the washing machine.
That covers loading your washing machine.
In next segment, we're going to discuss setting the water level on your washing machine itself.